lish.com 2012-10-04

# Shop What's Trending on the Social Web | Lish.com

Effective Date: February 5, 2011

Payvment takes your privacy very seriously and is committed to protecting your privacy and providing a means to allow you to safely make purchases on Facebook. This privacy statement describes how we collect and use the personal information you provide to Payvment. It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and the steps you can take to access this information and to ensure that it is accurate.

## Collection and Use of Personal Information

We collect and retain the following personal information when you make a purchase: Contact information such as your name, email address and shipping address.

We use the information we capture and collect to

  * Facilitate your transaction with our retailer clients
  * Retain your shipping information to pre-populate the form to make future product purchases easier.
  * Retain items you placed in your shopping cart if you leave the cart before completing your purchase

We do not use technologies such as cookies to track your activity on our application or to collect personal information from you.

## Information Sharing

We will share your personal information with third parties (such as shipping details to the retailer to facilitate a purchase) only in the ways that are described in this privacy statement. We do not sell your personal information to third parties.

We may also disclose your personal information:

  * as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process
  * when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request,
  * if Payvment is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information,
  * to any other third party with your prior consent to do so.

To help protect your privacy, we allow our retailer clients only limited access to your contact, shipping and financial information to facilitate your transactions. The use of your information is also subject to the retailer’s privacy statements. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy statement of any retailer you choose to make purchases from.

## PayPal

We use PayPal to collect and process payments. To complete your purchase, you will provide your credit card number, directly to PayPal. PayPal's privacy policy will apply to the information you provide on the PayPal website.

## Correcting and Updating Your Personal Information

To revise or delete your saved shipping information, you can click the “Your Settings” button on the Facebook storefront.

## Links to Other Web Sites

Our application includes links to other Web sites whose privacy practices may differ from those of Payvment’s. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is subject to their privacy statements. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy statement of any Web site you visit. If you post a comment or respond to a posting on a social network site, blog or Payvment fan page, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of those forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages.

## Security

The security of your personal information is important to us.

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

In order to make a purchase from us, you must use our payment provider to finalize and pay for your order. Its privacy statement and security practices will also apply to your information. We encourage you to read that privacy statement before providing your information.

If you have any questions about the security of our application, you can contact us at privacy@payvment.com

## Notification of Privacy Statement Changes

We may update this policy from time to time as our information practices are modified or changed. If we make any material changes to this policy that affect your personal information, we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on our application prior to the change. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices. Questions/Feedback

As an added step towards our commitment to your privacy, Payvment participates in the TRUSTe Privacy Seal Program, which requires members to fully disclose their information practices and undergo privacy compliance monitoring by TRUSTe. TRUSTe, a privacy services company dedicated to advancing privacy and online trust, certifies many companies to its leading privacy practices.

If you have any questions about the privacy or security of our website, you can send an e-mail to privacy@payvment.com or contact us via mail at the address below:

Payvment, Inc.  
Attn: Privacy  
250 Cambridge, Suite 301  
Palo Alto, CA 94306  

If this does not satisfactorily resolve your inquiry then you may contact TRUSTe at <http://www.truste.com/consumers/watchdog_complaint.php> and TRUSTe will then serve as a liaison with this company to resolve your concerns.

## Payvment Copyright Policy

Payvment respects the copyright law and expects its users to do the same. It is Payvment’s policy to terminate in appropriate circumstances Sellers, Shoppers or other users who repeatedly infringe or are believed to be repeatedly infringing the rights of copyright holders. 

#### Notification of Copyright Infringement:

Payvment, Inc. (“Payvment”) respects the intellectual property rights of others and we expect our sellers and shoppers to do the same.

It is Payvment’s policy, in appropriate circumstances and at its discretion, to disable and/or terminate the account or access of users who repeatedly infringe or are repeatedly charged with infringing the copyrights or other intellectual property rights of others. 

In accordance with the Digital Millennium Copyright Act of 1998, the text of which may be found on the U.S. Copyright Office website at <http://www.copyright.gov/legislation/dmca.pdf>, Payvment will respond expeditiously to claims of copyright infringement committed using a Payvment website or Payvment application (the “Sites and Application”) that are reported to Payvment’s Designated Copyright Agent, identified in the sample notice below. 

If you are a copyright owner, or are authorized to act on behalf of one, or authorized to act under any exclusive right under copyright, please report alleged copyright infringements taking place on or through the Site and Application by completing the following DMCA Notice of Alleged Infringement and delivering it to Payvment’s Designated Copyright Agent. Upon receipt of the Notice as described below, Payvment will take whatever action, in its sole discretion, it deems appropriate, including removal of the challenged material from the Site and Application. 

#### DMCA Notice of Alleged Infringement (“Notice”)

  1. Identify the copyrighted work that you claim has been infringed, or - if multiple copyrighted works are covered by this Notice - you may provide a representative list of the copyrighted works that you claim have been infringed.
  2. Identify the material that you claim is infringing (or to be the subject of infringing activity) and that is to be removed or access to which is to be disabled, and information reasonably sufficient to permit us to locate the material, including at a minimum, if applicable, the URL of the link shown on the Site and Application where such material may be found. 
  3. Provide your mailing address, telephone number, and, if available, email address.
  4. Include both of the following statements in the body of the Notice:
    * "I hereby state that I have a good faith belief that the disputed use of the copyrighted material is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent, or the law (e.g., as a fair use)."
    * "I hereby state that the information in this Notice is accurate and, under penalty of perjury, that I am the owner, or authorized to act on behalf of the owner, of the copyright or of an exclusive right under the copyright that is allegedly infringed." 
    * Provide your full legal name and your electronic or physical signature.

**Deliver this Notice, with all items completed, to Payvment’s Designated Copyright Agent:**

Copyright Agent  
c/o Payvment, Inc.  
250 Cambridge Avenue, Suite 301  
650-681-1580  
650-327-2564
